efactor.com 2009-06-18

# E.Factor

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:

The E.Factor will not sell, exchange, or otherwise share your personal identifiable information with third parties, unless we have to do so by law, with your prior consent or when we provide your details to a third party provider who delivers real benefits to you as a member of E.Factor. This last exchange of information will always be done under the strict understanding that said third party provides benefits to you directly but will not use your information in any other way other then for the explicitly agreed purpose.

The E.Factor does not spam or support the activities of spammers. Any sensitive information that you provide to us will be secured in accordance with industry standards. We also encourage you when you suspect a spammer is operating on the E.Factor, to bring it to our attention either via the "inappropriate behaviour" button in the MessageCentre, or by sending us an email at [security@efactor.com](mailto:security@efactor.com)

If we change the way in which we use your personally identifiable data and it will affect your materially, we will post this in this Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the E.Factor service after notice of changes has been sent to you or published on our site, we will take it that you therefore agree with our changed practices.

**Registration:**  
In order to become an E.Factor Service user, you have to create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, email address, country, ZIP/postal code, a brief summary of your professional background (current occupation & networking objectives), and you will have to choose a password.

**Profile Information**  
Once you are a user, you can always provide additional information in the profile section describing your skills, professional experiences, and networking objectives. Ofcourse it is entirely optional as to what additional information you provide beyond the minimum required at registration, but it will enable you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities in our system as well as it will improve the ability of other members to find you or your business.

**Information about your Contacts**  
To invite others to connect with you directly on the E.Factor, we ask you to copy in, or enter their names and email addresses. This information will be used by the E.Factor to send your invitation (including a message if you want) The names and email addresses of people that you invite will only be used to send your invitation and reminders.

You may also choose to manually enter or upload data about your contacts into the private "My Contacts" section of our website. All information entered there will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the E.Factor network without your permission.

All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will also be covered by this Privacy Policy.

**Cookies & Log Files**  
Like most web sites, [www.efactor.com](http://www.efactor.com/) uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows us to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.

One type of cookie, known as a "persistent" cookie, is set once you've logged in to your account. The next time you visit the E.Factor web site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as an existing user so you will not need to log in before using the service. In order to access or change any of your private information (like a credit card number), however, you must log in securely again with your password even if your computer contains your persistent cookie. Additionally, if you log out of the E.Factor site you will need to re-enter your password the next time you visit in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the E.Factor site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the E.Factor web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave the Service. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

**Children**  
Children cannot use the E.Factor. We therefore ask that minors (under the age of 18) do not submit any personal information to us or use the service.

**Information Use**  
The E.Factor Service is an online service dedicated to helping all types of professionals more effectively connect with one another. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual, is collected by us from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by the E.Factor. This information can be utilized by us in such manner as we, in our sole discretion, deem appropriate.

**E.Factor Service Communications**  
E.Factor Service will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. These include a series of welcome emails which help inform new users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Service related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. We may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to [info@efactor.com](mailto:info@efactor.com)

**Customized Content**  
Information you provide at registration or in your profile section is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we will display the screen names of new users who have recently joined your network or users whom have sent you an invite or other type of message.

**Sharing Information With Third Parties:**  
The E.Factor takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by position, industry, geographic location, company.

**Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services**  
The E.Factor partners with other (online) services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services it is always your choice to choose if you would like to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from the E.Factor to the partner if you choose to use the combined service. Please see also our section "Partners" for further information on who the current partners are.

**Communications Between Users**  
Many emails you initiate through the Service will list your E.Factor email address and name in the header of the message. Emails you initiate may also provide aggregate information about your network (for instance how many people are in your network), but will never list the people to whom you're directly connected unless you choose to show this to other users. Other communications that you initiate through the E.Factor website, like a request for contact or a question to a specific group, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information nor will it show the other users to whom the message is sent.. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated that you would like to establish contact with each other and that you accept messages from others.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**  
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your E.Factor account, at all times by logging into your account on the E.Factor website and editing the information via your own ControlRoom. You can also close your account through the E.Factor website. If you close your E.Factor account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the E.Factor Service, please send your request to [info@efactor.com](mailto:info@efactor.com). Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with E.Factor under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to [info@efactor.com](mailto:info@efactor.com) within three business days of our receiving it.

**Security**  
In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on the E.Factor Service is password-protected, and sensitive data (such as credit card information) is protected by SSL encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and our web site. To protect any data you store on our servers we also regularly audit our system for possible vulnerabilities and attacks and we use a tier-one secured-access data center.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
E.Factor may update this Privacy Policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@efactor.com](mailto:privacy@efactor.com) or contact us at:

**The E.Factor, Corp.**  
12 Desbrosses Street  
New York, NY 10013  
USA  
Attn: Privacy Policy
